Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
- Combat: Men, Not Heroes by Harold Calin Lancer 70-060 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 9)
- Combat: No Rest for Heroes by Harold Calin Lancer 72-910 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 9)
- The Courtship of Eddie's Father by Mark Toby Paperback Library 52-200 1961 (1st) (Box 9)
- Daktari by Jess Shelton Ace G-604 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 9)
- Daktari #1: Mystery at Wameru by Jess Shelton Souvenir 1860 ca. 1966 (Variant Cover) (Box 9)
- Daktari #2: The Pintu Dogs by Frank Denver Souvenir 1861 ca. 1967 (Box 9)
- Daktari #3: The Happy Hippo by Frank Denver Souvenir 1862 ca. 1967 (Box 9)
- Daktari #4: The Frighteners by Peter Leslie Souvenir 2232 ca. 1968 (Box 9)
- Dallas by Lee Raintree [Con Sellers] Dell 11752 ca. 1978 (1st) (White Cover) (Box 9)
- Dallas by Lee Raintree [Con Sellers] Dell 11752 ca. 1978 (1st new Dell: 1980) (Red Cover) (Box 9)
- The Ewings of Dallas by Burt Hirschfeld Bantam 14439 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 9)
- Dallas: The Quotations of J. R. Ewing by Diane J. Perlberg & Joelle Delbourgo, eds. Bantam 14440 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 9)
- The Women of Dallas by Burt Hirschfeld Bantam 14497 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 9)
- The Men of Dallas by Burt Hirschfeld Bantam 20390 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 9)
- The Official Dallas Trivia Book by Jason Bonderoff Signet AE3504 ca. 1984 (1st: 1985) (Box 9)
- Dallas #1: Love Conquers Fear by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 81 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 9)
- Dallas #2: Ardent Memories by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 82 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #3: Love's Challenge by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 83 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #4: The Power of Passion by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 84 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #5: Dangerous Desire by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 85 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #6: Double Dealing by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 86 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #7: Hostage Heart by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 87 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #8: This Cherished Land by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 88 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas#9: Power Play by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 89 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #10: Winner Take All by Paul Mantell & Avery Hart Pioneer 90 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #11: Reality Strikes by Mary Clare Kersten Pioneer 100 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #12: Shattered Dreams by Laura Taylor Pioneer 101 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dallas #13: A Cry in the Night by Monica Dean Pioneer 102 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 10)
- Danger Man: Target for Tonight by Richard Telfair [Richard Jessup] Dell First Edition K111 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #1 by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-386 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #1 by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-386 ca. 1966 (4th: 1968) (Variant Cover) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #2: Victoria Winters by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-421 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #2: Victoria Winters by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-421 ca. 1967 (2nd: 1968) (Variant Cover) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #3: Strangers at Collins House by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-543 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #3: Strangers at Collins House by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-543 ca. 1967 (2nd: 1968) (Variant Cover) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #4: The Mystery of Collinwood by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-610 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #4: The Mystery of Collinwood by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-610 ca. 1968 (3rd: 1968) (Variant Cover) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #5: The Curse of Collinwood by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 52-608 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #6: Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-001 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #7: The Secret of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-039 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #8: The Demon of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-084 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #9: The Foe of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-135 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #10: The Phantom of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-195 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #11: Barnabas Collins versus the Warlock by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-212 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #12: The Pearl of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 62-244 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #13: Barnabas Collins and the Mysterious Ghost by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-258 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 10)
- Dark Shadows #14: Barnabas Collins and Quentin's Demon by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-275 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #15: Barnabas Collins and the Gypsy Witch by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-296 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #16: Barnabas, Quentin and the Mummy's Curse by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-318 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #17: Barnabas, Quentin and the Avenging Ghost by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-338 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #18: Barnabas, Quentin and the Nightmare Assassins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-363 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #19: Barnabas, Quentin and the Crystal Coffin by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-385 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #20: Barnabas, Quentin and the Haunted Cave by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-402 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #21: Barnabas, Quentin and the Mummy's Curse by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-427 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #22: Barnabas, Quentin and the Frightened Bride by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-446 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #23: Barnabas, Quentin and the Scorpio Curse by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-468 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #24: Barnabas, Quentin and the Serpent by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-491 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #25: Barnabas, Quentin and the Magic Potion by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-515 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #26: Barnabas, Quentin and the Body Snatchers by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-534 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #27: Barnabas, Quentin and Dr. Jekyll's Son by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-554 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #28: Barnabas, Quentin and the Grave Robbers by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 63-585 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #29: Barnabas, Quentin and the Sea Ghost by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 64-663 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #30: Barnabas, Quentin and the Mad Magician by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 64-714 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #31: Barnabas, Quentin and the Hidden Tomb by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 64-772 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows #32: Barnabas, Quentin and the Vampire Beauty by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 64-824 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 11)
- Barnabas Collins in a Funny Vein Paperback Library 62-062 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 11)
- Barnabas Collins: A Personal Picture Album by Jonathan Frid, ed. Paperback Library 62-210 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 11)
- The Dark Shadows Book of Vampires and Werewolves by Barnabas and Quentin Collins, eds. Paperback Library 63-419 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- House of Dark Shadows by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library 64-537 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- The Dark Shadows Cookbook by Jody Cameron Malis Ace 13810 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 11)
- Dark Shadows Series Box Set: Dark Shadows, Victoria Winters, Strangers at Collins House, The Mystery of Collinwood, The Curse of Collinwood, Barnabas Collins, The Secret of Barnabas Collins, and The Demon of Barnabas Collins by Marilyn Ross Paperback Library ca. 1967 (Box 11)
- Days of Our Lives by Frances Forbes Popular Library 60-2397 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #1: Love's Shattered Dreams by Gillian Gorham Pioneer 51 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #2: Hearts Past Reason by Gillian Gorham Pioneer 52 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #3: Search for Love by Gillian Gorham Pioneer 53 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #4: Sentimental Longings by Gillian Gorham Pioneer 54 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #5: Passion's Lure by Serita Deborah Stevens Pioneer 55 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #6: Forsaken Dreams by Tara Lee Pioneer 56 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #7: Red Sky at Dawn by Stella Flint Pioneer 57 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #8: The Summer Wind by Nicloe Brooks Pioneer 58 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #9: Friends and Lovers by Nicole Brooks Pioneer 59 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #10: Promises and Lies by Marcia Lawrence Pioneer 60 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #11: Fantasies by Deidre Duncan Pioneer 150 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #12: Past Loves and Lies by Marcia Lawrence Pioneer 151 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #13: Crimes of the Heart by Nicloe Brooks Pioneer 152 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- Days of Our Lives #14: Obsessions by Marcia Lawrence Pioneer 153 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 12)
- The Defenders by Edward S. Aarons Gold Medal s1164 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 12)
- The Defenders: All the Silent Voices by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy] Pocket 50056 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 12)
- The Defenders: Ordeal by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy] Pocket 50107 ca. 1965 (1st (Box 12)
- 1964) (Box 12)
- The Defenders: Eve of Judgment by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy] Pocket 50190 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 12)
- The Deputy by Roe Richardson Dell First Edition B172 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 12)
- The Detectives by Norman Daniels Lancer 71-316 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 12)
- Divorce Court #1: Gilchrist vs. Gilchrist: A Question of Adultery by Jack Pearl Pocket 75667 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 12)
- Divorce Court #2: Lazer vs. Lazer: The Black Widow by Jack Pearl Pocket 75668 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 12)
- Young Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Avon F-133 ca. 1938,41 (1st: 1962) (Box 12)
- Calling Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Dell R123 ca. 1939,40 (1st: 1961) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare's Trial by Max Brand Dell R125 ca. 1941,42 (1st: 1962) (Box 12)
- The Secret of Dr. Kildare by Max Brand Dell 7712 ca. 1940 (1st: 1962) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare's Crisis by Max Brand Dell 1980 ca. 1940+ (1st (Box 12)
- 1962) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare's Search by Max Brand Dell 1981 ca. 1940+ (1st: 1962) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare Takes Charge by Max Brand Dell 1983 ca. 1940,41 (1st: 1962) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare by Robert C. Ackworth Lancer 71-308 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare by Robert C. Ackworth Lancer 71-308 ca. 1962 (3rd) (Box 12)
- Dr. Kildare's Secret Romance by Norman Daniels Lancer 70-007 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dr. Kildare's Finest Hour by Norman Daniels Lancer 70-032 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dr. Kildare: The Heart Has an Answer by William Johnston Lancer 70-043 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dr. Kildare: The Faces of Love by William Johnston Lancer 70-049 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who in an Exciting Adventure with the Daleks by David Whitaker Avon G1322 ca. 1964 (1st: 1967) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #1 and the Day of the Daleks by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40565 ca. 1974 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #2 and the Doomsday Weapon by Malcolm Hulke Pinnacle 40566 ca. 1974 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #3 and the Dinosaur Invasion by Malcolm Hulke Pinnacle 40606 ca. 1976 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #4 and the Genesis of the Daleks by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40608 ca. 1976 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #5 and the Revenge of the Cybermen by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40611 ca. 1976 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #6 and the Loch Ness Monster by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40609 ca. 1976 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #7 and the Talons of Weng-Chiang by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40638 ca. 1977 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #8 and the Masque of Mandragora by Philip Hinchcliffe Pinnacle 40640 ca. 1977 (1st: 1979) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #9 and the Android Invasion by Terrance Dicks Pinnacle 40641 ca. 1978 (1st: 1980) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #10 and the Seeds of Doom by Philip Hinchcliffe Pinnacle 40639 ca. 1977 (1st: 1980) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #1: Search for the Doctor [Find Your Fate] by David Martin Ballantine 33224 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #2: Crisis in Space [Find Your Fate] by Michael Holt [David Martin] Ballantine 33225 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #3: Garden of Evil [Find Your Fate] by David Martin Ballantine 33226 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #4: Mission to Venus [Find Your Fate] by William Emms Ballantine 33229 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #5: Invasion of the Ormazoids [Find Your Fate] by Philip Martin Ballantine 33231 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor Who #6: Race Against Time [Find Your Fate] by Pip & Jane barker Ballantine 33228 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 13)
- The Doctors by Michael Avallone Popular Library 08115 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 13)
- Doctor's Hospital #1: One of Our Own by Maud Willis [Eileen Lottman] Pocket 80231 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dragnet: Case 561 by David Knight [Richard S. Prather] Pocket 1120 ca. 1956 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dragnet: The Case of the Courteous Killer by Richard Deming Pocket 1198 ca. 1958 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dragnet: The Case of the Crime King by Richard Deming Pocket 1214 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dragnet: The Badge by Jack Webb Crest s341 ca. 1958 (1st: 1959) (Box 13)
- Dragnet 1968 by David H. Vowell Popular Library 60-8045 ca. 1967 (1st: 1968) (Box 13)
- The Dukes of Hazzard: Gone Racin' by Eric Alter Warner 30324 ca. 1982 (1st: 1983) (Box 13)
- Dynasty by Eileen Lottman Bantam 23352 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 13)
- Dynasty: Alexis Returns by Eileen Lottman Bantam 24431 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 13)
- The Edge of Night #1: The Seventh Mask by Henry Slesar Ace 18785 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 13)
- Eight is Enough by Tom Braden Crest 23002 ca. 1975 (4th: 1977) (Box 13)
- Eight is Enough by Tom Braden Crest 23002 ca. 1975 (6th: 1978) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: Lady, Lady, I Did it! by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4253 ca. 1961 (1st: 1962) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: The Con Man by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4264 ca. 1957 (2nd: 1962) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: Killer's Payoff by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4265 ca. 1958 (2nd: 1962) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: The Muggers by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4266 ca. 1956 (2nd: 1962) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: Killer's Choice by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4267 ca. 1958 (2nd: 1962) (Box 14)
- 87th Precinct: Cop Hater by Ed McBain [Evan Hunter] Perma M-4268 ca. 1956 (2nd: 1962) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: The Madman by Ellery Queen [Jack Vance] Signet Y6715 ca. 1966 (1st: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: The Finishing Stroke by Ellery Queen [Dannay/Lee] Signet Y6819 ca. 1958 (5th: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: Face to Face by Ellery Queen [Dannay/Lee] Signet Y6872 ca. 1967 (3rd: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: The House of Brass by Ellery Queen [Avram Davidson, from Dannay's story outline] Signet Y6958 ca. 1968 (3rd: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: Cop Out by Ellery Queen [Dannay/Lee] Signet Y6996 ca. 1969 (4th: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: The Last Woman in His Life by Ellery Queen [Dannay/Lee] Signet Y7123 ca. 1970 (4th: 1975) (Box 14)
- Ellery Queen: The Vanishing Corpse by Ellery Queen Pyramid V4094 ca. 1941 (3rd: 1976) (Box 14)
- Emergency! by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Popular Library 08198 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 14)
- Executive Suite by Cameron Hawley Popular Library 08578 ca. 1952 (unsp: 1977) (Box 14)
- Falcon Crest by Patrick Mann [Leslie Waller] Dell 12437 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 14)
- Family by Leila Andrews Ballantine 25570 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 14)
- Family #2: Transitions by Leila Andrews Ballantine 25705 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 14)
- Family #3: Commitments by Leila Andrews Ballantine 25706 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 14)
- Family Affair: Buffy's Cookbook by Jody Cameron Berkley W2092 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 14)
- Richard Dawson and Family Feud by Mary Ann Norbom Signet J9773 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 14)
- Family Ties: Alex Gets the Business by Joe Claro Avon 75235 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 14)
- Fantasy Island #1 by Jane Seskin Ballantine 27939 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 14)
- Fantasy Island #2 by Jane Seskin Ballantine 27940 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 14)
- Fantasy Island by Roger Elwood Weekly Reader F435 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 14)
- Father of the Bride by Edward Streeter Popular Library SP162 ca. 1948,49 (1st: 1962) (Box 14)
- The Felony Squad by Michael Avallone Popular Library 60-8036 ca. 1967 91st) (Box 14)
- Fish Strikes Out by T.J. Hemmings Ace Tempo Star 24005 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 14)
- Flight by Edgar Jean Bracco Berkley G291 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 14)
- Finstones Pocket 4262 ca. 1963 (Box 15)
- Flip Wilson Close-Up by James A. Hudson Avon V2459 ca. 1971 (1st: 1972) (Box 15)
- The Fifteenth Pelican by Tere Rios Avon ZS130 ca. 1965 (3rd: 1967) (Box 15)
- The Flying Nun: Miracle At San Tanco by William Johnston Ace G-702 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 15)
- The Flying Nun: The Littlest Rebels by William Johnston Ace G-725 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 15)
- The Flying Nun #3: Mother of Invention by William Johnston Ace 24300 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 15)
- The Flying Nun #4: The Little Green Men by William Johnston Ace 24301 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 15)
- The Flying Nun #5: The Underground Picnic by William Johnston Ace 24302 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 15)
- Frontier: 150 Years of the West by Luke Short, ed. [Frederick D. Glidden] Bantam A1401 ca. 1955 (1st) (Box 15)
- The Fugitive: Fear in Desert Town by Roger Fuller [Don Tracy] Pocket 35012 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 15)
- Fury: Stallions of Broken Wheel Ranch by Allen G. Miller Tempo T14 ca. 1959 (1st: 1962) (Box 15)
- Gadabout Gaddis: The Flying Fisherman by R.V. "Gadabout" Gaddis as told to George Sullivan Pocket 75224 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 15)
- Gadabout Gaddis: Secrets of Successful Fishing by Henry Shakespeare Dell First Edition M102 ca. 1962 (2nd: 1964) (Box 15)
- The Gangster Chronicles by Michael Lasker and Richard Alan Simmons [Richard Elman] Jove K5808 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 15)
- Garrison's Gorillas by Jack Pearl Dell 2798 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital by Burt Hirschfeld Lancer 70-055 ca. 1963 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital: Emergency Entrance by Burt Hirschfeld Lancer 72-917 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital: A Matter of Life and Death by Jane Horatio [Edythe Cudlippe] Award A858S ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital #2: Surgeon's Crisis by Bruce Cassiday Award AS1024 ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital #3: In the Name of Love by Bruce Cassiday Award AN1238 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 15)
- General Hospital #1/#2 [combined]: Forever and a Day, Book One and Two by Nicole Brooks (#1) and Marcia Lawrence (#2) Pioneer 300 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 15)
- Gentle Ben by Walt Morey Tempo T-166 ca. 1965 (1st: 1967) (Box 15)
- Gentle Ben by Walt Morey Scholastic Book Services TK1084 ca. 1965 (1st: 1967) (Box 15)
- Get Smart! by William Johnston Tempo T-103 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 15)
- Get Smart: Sorry, Chief by William Johnston Tempo T-119 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 15)
- Get Smart Once Again by William Johnston Tempo T-121 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 15)
- Get Smart #4: Max Smart and the Perilous Pellets by William Johnston Tempo T-140 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 15)
- Get Smart #5: Missed It By That Much! by William Johnston Tempo T-154 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 15)
- Get Smart #6: And Loving It! by William Johnston Tempo T-159 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 16)
- Get Smart #7: Max Smart - The Spy Who Went to the Cold by William Johnston Tempo T-174 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 16)
- Get Smart #8: Max Smart Loses Control by William Johnston Tempo T-191 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 16)
- Get Smart #9: Max Smart and the Ghastly Ghost Affair by William Johnston Tempo 05326 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 16)
- Get Smart: Would You Believe? by Don Adams & Bill Dana Bantam 20054 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 16)
- Getting Together by Judson McCall Curtis 07173 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 16)
- Getting Together #2: Bobby: Superstar by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Curtis 07180 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Ghost and Mrs. Muir by Josephine Leslie Pocket 77761 ca. 1945,72 (1st: 1974) (Box 16)
- The Ghost and Mrs. Muir by Alice Denham Popular Library 60-2348 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 16)
- Gidget in Love by Frederick Kohner Dell 2872 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 16)
- Gidget Goes Parisienne by Frederick Kohner Dell 2874 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 16)
- Gidget Goes New York by Frederick Kohner Dell 2897 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Girl From U.N.C.L.E. #1: The Birds of a Feather Affair by Michael Avallone Signet D3012 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Girl From U.N.C.L.E. #2: The Blazing Affair by Michael Avallone Signet D3042 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Girl From U.N.C.L.E. #4: The Cornish Pixie Affair by Peter Leslie Souvenir 1899 ca. 1967 (Box 16)
- The Girl With Something Extra by Paul W. Fairman Lancer 75491 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 16)
- Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C. by E. Kitzes Knox [Esther Kitzes and Helen Knox] Pyramid R-1267 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Gong Show Book by Jerry Bowles Ace Tempo Star 29814 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 16)
- The Green Hornet in the Infernal Light by Ed Friend [Richard Wormser] Dell 3231 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 16)
- Griff by Robert Weverka Bantam N8339 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 16)
- Growing Pains by N.H. Kleinbaum Bantam 26881 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 16)
- Kirk Cameron: Dream Guy by Grace Catalano Bantam 27135 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guestward Ho! by Barbara Hooton and "Patrick Dennis" [Edward Everett Tanner III] Popular Library SP71 ca. 1956 (unsp: 1960) (Box 16)
- The Guiding Light by Agnes Nixon Popular Library 60-8034 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #1: So Tender, So True by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 01 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #2: Two Lives, Two Loves by Francesca Evans [Lita Scott] Pioneer 02 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #3: Whispering Secrets, Hidden Hearts by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 03 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #4: Revenge of the Heart by Jean Frances Webb Pioneer 04 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #5: Rush to Love by Angelica Aimes [Lita Scott] Pioneer 05 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #6: Secret Passions by Kate Lowe Kerrigan [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 06 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #7: That Special Feeling by Kate Lowe Kerrigan [Frances Rickett] Pioneer 07 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #8: Restless Hearts by Marlene Creed Pioneer 08 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 16)
- Guiding Light #9: Playing With Fire by Marlene Creed Pioneer 09 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Guiding Light #10: Swept Away by Marlene Creed Pioneer 10 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Guiding Light #11: Hidden Fears by Virginia McDonnell Pioneer 11 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Guiding Light #12: Tender Loving Care by Marlene Creed Pioneer 12 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Guiding Light #13: Love's Fragile Web by Kacia Bennett Pioneer 13 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Guiding Light #14: Choices by Kacia Bennett Pioneer 14 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke by Don Ward Ballantine 236 ca. 1957 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke by Don Ward Ballantine 364K ca. 1957 (3rd: 1960) (Variant Cover) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Popular Library 08146 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke #1: The Renegades by Jackson Flynn [Donald Bensen] Award AN1283 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke #2: Shootout by Jackson Flynn [Gordon Shirreffs] Award AN1284 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke #3: Duel at Dodge City by Jackson Flynn [Donald Bensen] Award AN1328 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 17)
- Gunsmoke #4: Cheyenne Vengence by Jackson Flynn [Donald Bensen] Award AN1403 ca. 1974 (1st: 1975) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 1: Ready To Go Steady by William Johnston Tempo 05794 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 2: Fonzie Drops In by William Johnston Tempo 07452 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days: Fonzie Drops In by William Johnston Ace Tempo Star 24515 ca. 1974 (1st Tempo Star: 1977) (Variant Cover) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 3: The Invaders by William Johnston Tempo 12267 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 17)